校长:注意,
Principal: Attention, attention please.I am the principal, Lewis Dewitt.
请大家注意了.我是校长刘易斯·德威特,
For the benefit of those of you who haven't bothered to attend the single
为了那些四年中一次家长会也没参加过的家长更好的了解我们.
PTA meeting in the past four years.
本:不不!
Ben: No, no hold it.
等等.我妈妈可不会缺席迈克的毕业典礼,
My mom won't miss Mike's graduation from the world,
怎么现在她又去洗手间了.
and now she is darn in that bathroom again.
开萝尔:本,这真是烦人!
Carol: I annoy ya Ben!
本:那不是妈妈的错,妈妈是怀孕了,我想应该怪爸爸的.
Ben: It's not my mom's fault.She's pregnant and I mean you see Dad.
校长:不要紧.
Principal: Never mind.
杰森:我们迟到了,并且还引起了骚动.
Jason: We've arrived late and created scenes.
麦琪:我们又不是故意要这样的,大家怎么还这样瞪着我?
Maggie: We are not going to create scenes.Why is everyone staring at us?
杰森:那是你自己想象的.
Jason: That's your imagination.
校长:我想你们一定认识19频道的新闻主播麦琪·马龙.
Principal: I'm sure you all recognized Maggie Malone from the channel 19 news.
本:要是那老太太肯移一下位置,这里就刚好有四个座位.
Ben: Here is four seats if we can get the old lady to move.
开萝尔:走,走,我们快点.
Carol: Go.Go.Let's go.
麦琪:快点坐.
Maggie: Take them quickly.
杰森:本,你别叫了.
Jason: Ben, stop yelling.Excuse me, would you like moving down.
对不起,你能不能往那边移一下,我妻子想坐在走道边上.
My wife loves to seat down on the aisle.
老妇人:知道了.
The old lady: We heard.
校长:这样坐着舒服吗?
Principal: comfy?
麦琪:是的.
Maggie: Yes.
校长:女士们,
Principal: Ladies and gentlemen,
先生们!
we are gathered here today in the Elizabeth Long Devil Memorial Auditorium
我们今天聚集在伊丽莎白·朗·德维尔纪念大礼堂里,为杜威中学98届的同学举行毕业典礼,
to pay tribute to the Dewey High School class of 1998.
而且每个人都要自豪的站到台上来.
And here are your hooters, standing tall and proud.
迈克:我成功了,我终于成功了.我终于从这所学校你也了.
Mike: I did it.I actually did it.I actually made it through this school.
不,我不能这样说,否则会倒霉的.
No I didn't say that.I don't want to jinx it.
麦琪:他成功了,我的孩子终于做到了.
Maggie: He did it.My baby, I truly did it.
杰森:迈克,你的确要从这所中学毕业了.
Jason: Mike, you actually made it through high school.
开萝尔:哇!他成功了,这我可没想过,不然我会倒霉的.
Carol: Wow, did it.I didn't think that, I don't want to jinx this.
本:我讨厌这套衣服.
Ben: I hate this weenie suit.
校长:谢谢你,
Principal: Thank you, Mr.
布扎德先生.
Buzzard; the hooter madrigals have never sounded sweeter.
你们今天德校歌唱得真好,并祝你们在新的学校了也能取得优异的成绩.
And I wish you well at your new school.
下面有请我们学生会主席理查德·斯塔伯恩讲话.
I would like to present you the student body president Richard Stabone.
波纳·斯塔伯恩:德威特校长,汉·道伊副校长,沃苏西奥先生和各位到会者,老同学们,新同学们,欢迎你们!我记得多年以前,我们刚参加……
Boner Stabone: Principal Dewitt, vice principal Han Doy, Mr.Verssucio and the attention.Past hooters
future hooters, carried hooters, welcome.
Full score and several years ago, we attended
麦琪:我们的孩子要毕业了,那些过去的日子真是令人难忘啊!
Maggie: And my baby is graduating.Where did the years go?
波纳·斯塔伯恩:而现在我们都已经成材了
Boner Stabone: And resulting millennium.
杰森:把头稍微转一下,好的,你俩都笑笑.
Jason: Turn your head just a little.All right, both of you Smile.
麦琪:迈克才一个月大,难道你认为他会……
Maggie: Mike is only a week old.Do you really think that..?
杰森:哦!麦琪,他笑的很好,你不要讲话了.
Jason: Ah!Maggie, he was smiling perfectly.Don't talk.
麦琪:你要对你爸爸稍微耐心一点,
Maggie: You are going to have to be a little patient with your Daddy's
因为他以前从没当过父亲.
never been a father before.
杰森:麦琪,笑一笑,迈克.
Jason: Maggie, say cheese, Mikey.
麦琪:快点,杰森.
Maggie: Hurry, Jason.
杰森:我要等到他脸上出现笑意的时候再拍,哦,
Jason: I want to get just the right expression.On his little...
麦琪,你看看你!
Oh, Maggie, you yawned.
麦琪:对不起,杰森.哦,宝贝,抱歉让你受苦了.
Maggie: I am sorry Jason!Oh baby, I am sorry to put you through this.
杰森,没事的,
Jason: All right, I got lots of more films.
我还有很多胶.你看,每张照片里他都在笑.
You know, he was smiling perfectly in every shot.
麦琪:哦,杰森,他没有在笑.
Maggie: Oh, Jason, he was not.
杰森:他天生爱笑,和你一样.
Jason: He is a smiler, and takes after his Mom.
麦琪:甜心,这么小的婴儿不会笑的.
Maggie: Sweetheart, babies his age do not smile.
杰森:布,那为什么每张照片里他都好像在笑.
Jason: No, why didn't it look like he was smiling in every shot.
麦琪:那是他在放屁.
Maggie: He has gas.
杰森:迈克,这点你也像你妈妈.
Jason: Mike, like I said he takes after his Mom.
麦琪:哦,杰森,他是像我.
Maggie: Oh, Jason, he is.
杰森:哦,我只是开个玩笑让你们露出笑脸好拍摄.
Jason: Oh just a little joke.Just to get the right expression.
麦琪:哦,杰森,你的房里有个婴儿.
Maggie: Oh, Jason, there is a baby in our room.
杰森:快叫警察.
Jason: Call the police.
麦琪:妈妈来了.
Maggie: Here comes Mommy.
杰森:亲爱的,要不是只有你能喂奶,我倒是很想帮你.
Jason: Honey, only you were breast-feeding, boy I sure like to help you out here.
麦琪:我知道了,我的小淘气!你是不是想吃宵夜啊?好吧!好吧!快吃吧!宝贝,看来你是真的饿了.告诉你件事,妈妈不会介意半夜以来给你喂奶的,因为那是妈妈乐意做的事,宝贝,你是不是很惊奇啊!别告诉你爸爸,我要让他觉得内疚.我的小宝淘气,再过多久我们就不能半夜里聊天了,因为你就会去幼儿园,然后小学,再中学,再大学,然后是白宫.
Maggie: I know.Hi little boy, do you want mid-night snack huh?Yes.Yes
yes.Child, my big guy, he is really hungry.One more secret, I don't mind
giving you up in the middle night for you at all.That's the kind I
like.Dear, surprise me too.Don't tell your father, I like him feeling guilty.
My
little guy, before you know it, we won't be having this night talks any more
You will be going to the kindergarten, then grammar school, then high school,
then college
and then the White House
麦琪:是的,这样很好.你不会不踢我啊?哦,走路了!你居然能走路了!等你爸爸回来我就告诉他.
Maggie: Yeah, right.Kick me a little Republican can you?Oh, you are walking.Oh
aren't you some thing?Wait till I tell your daddy when he gets home
麦琪对电视说:你最好这样!
Maggie to TV: You better!
杰森:哦,他是该这样的.
Jason: Oh, he's.
麦琪:太好了.
Maggie: Great.
波纳·斯塔伯恩:不要问学校能为你做什么?而是问你自己的学校能为国家做什么?
Boner Stabone: Ask not what will your school can do for you,
谢谢.
ask what your school can do for your country.Thank you.
开萝尔:妈妈,这并不是一个精彩的演讲.
Carol: Mom, It wasn't that great a speech...
麦琪:什么演讲?
Maggie: What speech?
杰森:我真是到底给谁鼓掌?不过没关系,
Jason: What the hell am Iapplauding for?It doesn't matter.
我儿子就要毕业了.
My son is graduating.
杰森:嘿!迈克,你在做什么?
Jason: Hey, Mikey, Mikey.What are you doing?
迈克:我在阅读.
Mike: Reading.
杰森:那你就不要把书撕了,书本可是我们的好朋友.
Jason: We don't tear books apart.No, books are our friends.
迈克:对不起.
Mike: I'm sorry.
杰森:好的,现在你坐到爸爸的腿上来,
Jason: Ok, then.You come up here sitting on daddy's knees,
我想给你读一个故事.
because I am going to read you a story.
迈克:布.
Mike: No.
杰森:好了,来吧!
Jason: Yeah, come on,
我想让你看看书本里面的精彩世界.
I want you to see what the wonderful worlds there are in the exciting books.
迈克:不,不,不!
Mike: No.No.No.No.
杰森:嘘!你别把开萝尔吵醒了.
Jason: Hush....You're gonna wake up Carol.
迈克:布.
Mike: No.
杰森:迈克,来吧,你怎么就这么讨厌书呢?
Jason: Mike, come on, what have you got against books?
迈克:我恨书,我想去玩.
Mike: I hate them.I want to play.
杰森:等等,但你需要读书呀!只有接受教育,你才能……
Jason: wait, But you are going to need books.You know for your education.So
you can
迈克:不,我不想去学校念书,我不去.
Mike: No, I'm not going to school.I decide.
杰森:好吧,那你长大了靠什么养活自己?
Jason: Ok, what are you going to earn a living when you grow up?
迈克:靠玩.
Mike: Play.
杰森:来吧!迈克,你会慢慢喜欢学校的生活的.
Jason: Come on, Mike, you are going to love your first day at school.
开萝尔:我希望自己现在就能去学校念书.
Carol: I wish I was old enough to go to school.
迈克:闭嘴,开萝尔.
Mike: Shut up, Carol.
开萝尔:不.
Carol: No.
迈克:闭嘴.
Mike: Yes.
开萝尔:不.
Carol: No.
迈克:闭嘴
Mike: Yes.
杰森:嘿!孩子们,别吵了.
Jason: Hey, hey, hey, kids, kids.
麦琪:迈克,你看学校多有趣!
Maggie: Mike, You see how much fun it is!
迈克:你带我去看牙医的时候也是这么说的!
Mike: That's what you said when we went to the dentist!
杰森:哦,你看那边也有一个和你一样大的小男孩.
Jason: Oh ho, ho, ho, Look, there is another little boy just your age.
他穿着校服,你瞧他多开心呀!
He is all dressed up for school.He looks so happy.
麦琪:来吧,迈克,不要错过校车了.
Maggie: Come on.Mike you're gonna miss the bus.
迈克:爸爸妈妈,你们让我自己上校车吧!
Mike: Daddy, Mommy, could you let me go to the bus by myself.
我不想让别人觉得我是个笨蛋.
I don't want to look like a weed.
麦琪:哦,我是不放心你一个人穿过马路.
Maggie: Oh, you have to cross the street.And I just...
杰森:哦,迈克,你能行的!
Jason: Oh, sure, Mikey.Yeah!
麦琪:好吧,迈克,祝你今天过得愉快!他会很好的.
Maggie: Well, Ok, Mikey.Have a great first day.He will be ok.
杰森:会好的.
Jason: Be fine.
开萝尔:是的.
Carol: Yeah, right.
波纳·斯塔伯恩:嘿!
Boner Stabone: Hi!
迈克:嘿!
Mike: Hi!
波纳·斯塔伯恩:你叫什么?
Boner Stabone: What's your name?
迈克:迈克·西沃.
Mike: Mikey Seaver.
波纳·斯塔伯恩:我叫迪基·斯塔伯恩.
Boner Stabone: I am Dickey Stabone.
迈克:迪基,你的名字真是难听.
Mike: Dickey, that's a pretty stupid name.
波纳·斯塔伯恩:是的,我讨厌这个名字.
Boner Stabone: Yeah, yeah, it is.I hate it.
迈克:邦先生?邦尼?邦?波纳?那现在开始,你就叫波纳.
Mike: Mr.Bon?Bonny?Bon?Boner?Yeah, from now on your name is Boner.
波纳·斯塔伯恩:但我的内衣上都是写着迪基,你干得真好,迈克.
Boner Stabone: But all the names tagged on my underwear say Dickey.Well-it works Michael.
迈克:是的,波纳,我们干得好.
Mike: Yea, we did it, Boner.
波纳·斯塔伯恩:波纳这名字我喜欢,我才不管我的内衣上写着什么呢!
Boner Stabone : Boner.I like that.I don't care what's on my underwear.
迈克:爸爸!
Mike: Daddy!
杰森:迈克,今天过的怎么样?学校如何?
Jason: Mikey, how's my boy?How was the school?
迈克:今天我真想你,我在学校想了你一天.
Mike: Boy, I missed you today.I thought about you all the time.
杰森:哦,那学校怎么样?
Jason: Oh.How was the school today?
迈克:你是世界上最好的爸爸.
Mike: I must have the best dad on earth.
杰森:学校怎么样?
Jason: How was the school?
迈克:爸爸,我爱你.
Mike: I love you daddy.
杰森:迈克,好了,我问你学校怎么样?哦,我也爱你.
Jason: Mike, come on, and I was asking how.Oh, I love you too.
麦琪:嘿,亲爱的.
Maggie: Hi, Honey.
杰森:哦,嘿!甜心.
Jason: Oh, Hi, sweet heart.
麦琪:嘿!迈克,你有没有把你的成绩单给你爸爸看看.
Maggie: Hi, Mikey, did you tell you dad about your report card?
迈克:呃!哦!
Mike: Er, Oh.
杰森:哦!
Jason: Oh!
迈克:正想要说.
Mike: just about to ..
麦琪:那好,你说吧!迈克.
Maggie: Well, Go ahead, Mike.
迈克:我爱你,妈妈.
Mike: I love you, Mommy.
麦琪:这招不会对我们起作用的,我们不是笨蛋.
Maggie: Look that won't work on us sweet heart.We are not stupid.
迈克:但是会对爸爸起作用.
Mike: It worked on daddy.
校长:谢谢你们,多好的歌,多好的结尾.
Principal: Thank you for that.A stirring song.Stirring ending.Hahahaha!
哈哈!我看就到这里吧.我们已经让我们的毕业生等得着急了,
I see, there is no reason to prolong this.
哈哈!埃斯特拉,把毕业证书给我.
I keep our nervous graduates in suspense.Hahaha!Estelle, the diplomas!
迈克:成了!
Mike: This is it.
杰森:成了!
Jason: This is it.
麦琪:成了!
Maggie: This is it.
开萝尔:成了!
Carol: This is it.
本:我饿了.
Ben: I am hungry.
老妇人:要是他以为这样就算毕业,那他一定是脑子有问题.
The old lady: If he thinks he is getting this, he almost is crazy.
迈克:不是我做的,我没碰到她,我可以发誓.
Mike: I didn't do it.I didn't touch the woman, I swear.
校长:没关系,埃斯特拉,你能不能快点?
Principal: No harm done.Estelle, would you hurry up?Accidents will happen.
这是意外!快把毕业证书给我,要不你就给我滚蛋.
I want those diplomas now, or you are gone.
马绍尔:我已经在尽力了.
Marshall: I do with the best I can.
校长:你是怎么在这里混饭吃的?我看我们还是请布扎德先生再给大家指挥一首小曲!
Principal: How would you survive if you had to get a real job.
Why don't we have Mr.
Buzzard herald the choirs to do another little ditty for us?
埃斯特拉:给你.
Estelle: Here.
校长:谢谢你,布扎德先生,谢谢.好了,我们讲到哪里了?好吧,是毕业证书!下面我按字母顺序一个一个叫你们,你们再上来拿证书.爱德华?科利尼厄斯,就是你!下面是……
Principal: Thank you!Mr.Buzzeard.Thank you.Okey Dokey.Where were we?All right, yes, the diplomas.Class, I'll be calling your names in alphabetical, order.Edward?Cornelius, Diza.Get down, you Mr.
迈克和波纳:科利尼厄斯
Mike and Bonner: Cornelius.
校长:扎夫?你先坐下,
Principal: Zaff?Then you sit down, Mr..
埃斯特拉先生,你不是说名字是按字母顺序排的吗?
Estelle, Estelle, I thought these were in alphabetical order!?.
埃斯特拉:我以为你已经排了.
Estelle: I know you did.
校长:那就算了吧!扎夫先生,是不是要我亲自请你上来吗?
Principal: This is just great.Mr.Zaff, What are you in need of a great invitation?
开萝尔:这典礼刚好合适迈克.
Carol: This is a perfect graduation for Mike.
本:为什么?
Ben: Why?
开萝尔:因为简直像小丑表演似的.
Carol: Because it stinks.
本:开萝尔,你的牙齿上粘着东西.
Ben: Carol, You got something stuck between your teeth.
开萝尔:什么?
Carol: What?
本:真是恶心.
Ben: it's really ugly.
开萝尔:我的牙齿上没有东西呀!
Carol: There is nothing in between my teeth.
本:你的耳朵上也没什么东西
Ben: So there is nothing in between your ears either.
开萝尔:好啊!你在帮迈克说话,
Carol: Fine, defend Mike.What's this?For Carol, personal.
那是什么?请开萝尔亲自拆开,胖妞!
P-u-r-s-i-n-a-l.
开萝尔:那是迈克写的.
Carol: That's Mike.
迈克:哦,你这笨蛋,你还欠我50美元,利息从1974年7月4日开始算起,迈克.
Mike: Ok, sucker, you owe me 50 bucks plus interest from July 4th 1976, Mike.
开萝尔:1974年7月4日
Carol: July 4th 1976?
迈克:就是那天.
Mike: That's what I said.
麦琪:亲爱的,你快看那些大船.
Maggie: Honey, look at the tall ships.
杰森:哦,是的,他们真是漂亮.
Jason: Oh Well.That's beautiful.
迈克:妈妈你看,爸爸说的对,你用不着化妆.
Mike: See, Mommy.Dad is right.We don't need color.
杰森:谢谢你,迈克.
Jason: Thanks, Mikey.
迈克:我也想去看看.
Mike: I want to go watch too.
杰森:不不!儿子,这得到你完成你的作业之后.
Jason: No, no, no.Not until you finish your reading, our son.
开萝尔:哈哈!
Carol: ha...
麦琪:开萝尔,别吵他了.
Maggie: Leave him alone Carol.
你哥哥这个暑假又很多功课要做.
Your brother has a lot of catching up to do this summer.
杰森:来吧,迈克,快读这行.
Jason: Come on, Mikey.Read this line.
迈克:我讨厌这本书.
Mike: I hate this book.
杰森:哦,亲爱的,你是怎么就知道会讨厌这本书呢?你还没有度过呢!
Jason: Oh honey, How do you know it?You haven't even read it yet.
迈克:我已经听说过这本书了,我想看电影.
Mike: I heard about it.I'll just wait for the movie.
杰森:迈克?
Jason: Mike?
迈克:好了,好了!不用你帮忙.
Mike: Ok, Ok.Don't help me.s, s.
开萝尔:爸爸说"看他跑",跑,跑,跑!看他在摇他的尾巴.
Carol: "See Sport run" said dad.Run run run.See him wag his tail.
杰森:麦琪,你听到她说的了吗?
Jason: Maggie, did you hear her?
麦琪:听到了,她会读书了,她居然四岁就会读书.
Maggie: I heard, she could read.Four years old, she can read.
杰森:这真是个奇迹.
Jason: It's a miracle.
麦琪:简直令人难以置信.
Maggie: It's fantastic.
杰森:哦,她是个小天才.
Jason: Oh, a little genius.
麦琪:哦,我要打电话告诉爸爸妈妈.
Maggie: Oh, I've got to go to call Mom and dad.
杰森:哦,我去找个录音机.
Jason: Oh, I've got to take the recorder.
开萝尔:把书翻过了,让我看看接着会怎么样?
Carol: Turn the page.I want to see how it comes out.
迈克:你是不是很高兴看到我出丑呀?不是吗?
Mike: Always got to make me feel bad, don't you?
开萝尔:是的.
Carol: yeah.
迈克:你别太嚣张了,你就会这点,那也没什么大不了的.
Mike: Big deal.So what if you can read?It does not mean nothing.
开萝尔:当然是了不起了,这说明我是聪明的,而你是愚蠢的,你以后是毕不了业的.
Carol: Sure, it does.It means I am smart, and you are stupid.You'll not even gonna to graduate.
迈克:我愿意拿50美元和你打赌.
Mike: I bet you fifty bucks, I do.
开萝尔:好吧,你这笨蛋.
Carol: Ok, sucker.
迈克:你知不知道什么叫毕业?好了,你这笨蛋,你还欠我50美元,利息从1974年7月4日开始算起.
Mike: What does graduate mean?Ok, sucker you owe me fifty bucks and interest from
July 4th 1976.Mike
校长:迈克·西沃.不,等等,我念错了.
Principal: Michale Seaver.No, wait.That's a mistake.
迈克:什么?
Mike: What?
全家:什么?
The family: What?
校长:应该是迈克·基默,祝贺你!
Principal: Should read Mike Kilmer.Jeez!
迈克:他是故意的.
Mike: He did that on purpose.
波纳·斯塔伯恩:迈克,你想不想看看我的证书?
Boner Stabone: Mike, wanna see my diploma?
迈克:哦,当然,波纳·斯塔伯恩.
Mike: Oh, sure.Boner Stabone.
波纳:这是我的.
Boner: It's me.
迈克:你的毕业证书上怎么也是写着波纳?
Mike: You have a Boner on the diploma?
波纳:是的,这很好呀!
Bonner: Yea, it cost extra.
迈克:波纳是我们小孩时我给你起的,现在听起来是个愚蠢的名字.
Mike: Boner was fine when we were kids.It's gotta be a pretty stupid name.
波纳:是吗?对,是很难听,我讨厌这名字.
Bonner: Yeah?Yes, it is.I hate it.
迈克:是的,叫理查德不错,或者你可以叫里克.
Mike: Yeah, Richard is not that bad.Or, hey, hey what about Rick?
波纳:里克·斯塔伯恩?是的,他们会喜欢的.当然我妈妈得要在我的内衣上改一下名字.
Boner: Rick Stabone?Yea, they're gonna love it.Of course my Mom is gonna have
to change all the tags on my underwear
Ben: Hello, Pony, can you hear me?Can you hear me?Now we are trapped
by them on the four sides.Make them three.Where are you?Tanks!Oh no
I touched a grenade!Hit it George O.Willis!Kabooey
杰森:这是哥哥的毕业典礼,你能不能安静点?
Jason: It's your brother's graduation.Will you please stop exploding.
校长:我们最后一张毕业证书也发了,现在毕业典礼就此结束.
Principal: And that's our last diploma.That concludes our graduation ceremony.
迈克:不!
Mike: no.
全家:不!
The family: No.
迈克:那肯定不是最后一张,难道就没有了?
Mike: That can't be all of them.There 's gotta be one more?
校长:埃斯特拉,呵呵!还有一张被我踩在脚下了.
Principal: Estelle, Hehehehe.Yes, I stepped on it.
埃斯特拉:你不是已经说完了.
Estelle: You said it.
校长:迈克·阿兰·西沃
Principal: Michael Alan Seaver.
迈克:到!
Mike: Yes.
杰森:你高心吗?
Jason: Enjoying yourself?
迈克:是的,我很放松,爸爸
Mike: Yea.I am just relaxing, Dad.
杰森:是的,那好吧!你晚上早点睡,明天还要参加毕业典礼呢!你上当了!
Jason: Yes, good.Oh, you had better get to bed, school tomorrow?Gotcha!
迈克:好的,现在回想起自己过去的一切,真是有点不敢相信自己要毕业了!
Mike: Well, yeah, now it's kinda hard getting used to the idea that all that junk is behind me now.
杰森:是的,不过还没结束.
Jason: Well, don't.
迈克:什么?
Mike: What?
杰森:德威特先生刚刚打电话过来说他们重新计算了你的学分.
Jason: Mr.Dewitt called they rechecked your records.
迈克:爸爸?
Mike: Dad?
杰森:你又被骗了,好了,只是个玩笑!
Jason: Gotcha again!Well, this is fun.
迈克:是的,那真是个不小的玩笑.
Mike: Yes, it's a real hoot.
杰森:事实上你一直都很努力学习,现在你是该休息一下了.
Jason: The truth is you worked very hard.And you deserve a rest.
迈克:你讲得对.
Mike: That's right.
杰森:是该让你放松一下,好好休息休息.
Jason: This is your time now, relax and kick back, have some fun.
迈克:是的.
Mike: Yes.
杰森:特别是再过三个星期,兰登高等专科学校的暑期班就要开学了.
Jason: Especially since the summer session of Alf Landen Junior collage starts in about three weeks.
迈克:不不!你这下又是在开玩笑吧?
Mike: No, no, no, no.You didn't get me that time, dad.
杰森:好了,这次我可是认真的.
Jason: Well, That time I was not joking.
迈克:你是开玩笑的.
Mike: You are joking.
杰森:不.
Jason: No.
迈克:好吧,爸爸.我其实早就想和你说一件事,本来我跟你说是要去兰登高等专科学校的,但上个星期我又改主意了,这是我认真考虑了很久的主意,我想现在是告诉你的最好时机了.
Mike: Well.You know, dad.I have been wanting to talk to you about that.See, you know, I know that I told you that I was planning to go
to Alf Landen, but in the last couple of weeks, I've been doing some serious
thinking.And, well I think now it's the best time to let you know about
my decision
杰森:什么?
Jason: What?
迈克:是这样的,波纳和我已经报名参加海军了.
Mike: Well, Boner and I have been listed in the marines.
杰森:迈克,你等会.
迈克:你也上当了吧!
00:23:26,800
Jason: Mike, Well, wait a minute. Mike: Got ya!